Fighting countries can still love...
Tristan & Isolde is a drama, romance film directed by Kevin Reynolds.
An affair between the second in line to Britain's throne and the princess
of the feuding Irish spells doom for the young lovers.
Tristan, played by James Franco.
Isolde, played by Sophia Myles.
Marke, played by Rufus Sewell.
Donnchadh, played by David O'Hara.
Wictred, played by Mark Strong.
Melot, played by Henry Cavill.
Tristan & Isolde is a 2006 epic romantic drama film directed by Kevin Reynolds and written by
Dean Georgaris based on the medieval romantic legend of Tristan and Isolde.
Produced by Ridley Scott (who had been working on an adaptation since the mid-1970s) and Tony Scott, the film stars James
Franco and Sophia Myles, alongside a supporting cast featuring Rufus Sewell, Mark Strong, and Henry Cavill.
This was Franchise Pictures' last film after the 2004 bankruptcy.
The film explores themes of in love with enemy,
hostility, castle, lovers, revenge.
The tone is emotional.